https://directoils.co.uk/terms/

Search
SearchHomeInfo & AdviceSolid Shampoo CompanyProductsAromatherapy Essential Oils & Carrier OilsFragrance KitsINCENSE STICKS & CONESMens StuffContact UsMy AccountFruity Fragrance OilsFloral Fragrance OilsSpicy Fragrance OilsOther MixesFestive Fragrance OilsAromatherapy FragrancesPerfume Fragrance OilsSign InHomeInfo & AdviceSolid Shampoo CompanyProductsAromatherapy Essential Oils & Carrier OilsFragrance KitsINCENSE STICKS & CONESMens StuffContact UsMy Account
Return to previous pageHome Terms and Conditions  Privacy PolicyDirectOils.co.uk – Privacy PolicyAt DirectOils.co.uk, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalised service. Please read on for more detail about our privacy policy.  What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It?When you make your on line payment, we need to know your name, email address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and expiry date and CSV number. This allows us to process and fulfil your orders and notify you of your order status.  How Does DirectOils.co.uk Protect Customer Information?When you make a payment or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, as required by the UK Data Protection Acts of 1984 and 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information you have provided to us, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.  Will DirectOils.co.uk Disclose Customer Information to 3rd Parties?Directoils.co.uk does not sell, trade or rent any customer information to any 3rd parties. Customer Information is not shared by DirectOils.co.uk to any 3rd parties.Directoils.co.uk is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on our website to make our services at Directoils.co.uk possible and to enhance your overall browsing and purchasing experience. We do not sell, share, trade or rent your personal information to others.  Your ConsentBy using directoils.co.uk you consent to the collection and use of your information by Directoils.co.uk. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will inform our customers via this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.  ReturnsThe Consumer Contracts (Information, Cancellation and Additional Charges) Regulations 2013As per the above legislation all goods can be returned within a 14 day period. It is our responsibility to supply goods that meet your customer rights and expectations. If you have any concerns that we have not met our legal obligations please contact us. Should you change your mind about the goods you receive please return them within 14 days of informing us of your decision to cancel. The cost and safe delivery of returns is the responsibility of the consumer.© 2019 Direct Oils
